that's a provocative question to which
you will not get an answer
hey guys welcome to stir crazy you know
my guest today from star trek and wonder
woman he's a fantastic actor and his
eyes are so blue i think he might be cgi
it's chris pine hey dude how are you
look at your psychedelic backdrop are
you having a rave there what's going on
raves here every day i've been talking
to you for many years so i think you
know this but
i'm going to say this for the record
you're my favorite chris
i just went out there i feel like i'm
the underdog right now so i'll take
all the support i can i can get do you
have a leaderboard at home do you like
when when evans like
wears the cool christmas sweater last
year are you like he's in the lead
what the
yeah those damn chris's man i just you
know it's either change my name or
really just
step it up you know here's my idea all
the chris's come together for an
avengers
style movie we call it the christening
this this make all you guys need to do
is just sit around in cute sweaters for
two hours that makes two billion dollars
you know shoot man maybe either we do
like uh maybe it's just a comic-con
a chris a con like uh
like a rat pack show at the sands you
know
where we we entertain and do a bit of
vaudeville
and you yeah you're getting a lot of
attention in wonder woman 1984 not only
for your fantastic performance but
the amazing style that you rock i am
crediting you with bringing back the
fanny pack but i want to see if you can
bring back
any fashion i'm going to show you some
retro fashions you tell me if this works
yes all day yes a don
johnson first is that my face
yes i look good look at that
look at that hair are you ready
to tan that much though
sure he looks great
to be fair i feel like this is already
in your wardrobe this is not so far off
to be fair
look at that shirt it's like a silk
basketball jersey
what do you think yes of course i'd wear
that
is that a full leather yeah i'd say
no to the hair okay yes to the polka dot
definitely to the guitar 100 million
percent to the
matching leather outfit
of course front of stair of course
are you kidding me now that takes a lot
of upkeep though
i've actually i want to do i'd like to
bring back the top hat
you can do it if any man can do it but i
could try i could certainly try
if you had showed up today just wearing
a top hat and like a monocle i would
have been mr monopoly
is living it's good it works are
interesting i've never
totally understood when they put the
monocle in are they flexing
face muscles to keep the monocle in or
does the monocle somehow
just fit into that cavity right there
yeah because you're gonna like
that's that's that's exhausting yeah
that will hurt after a while
so this is a little nosferatu action
that's your face what do you think
if any man can bring back the high power
look at my face in there i mean
i don't you know i look on a daily i
don't know if i can i
you know on a daily i like uh i like a
nice
espresso cup and those right those nails
aren't doing it but
uh yeah you're not you're not trying to
play that that feels like a gary a woman
character i could do that
you're not you're not willing to not uh
cut your nails for a year just for high
fashion
i would be willing to not cut my nails
for a year if that meant i could play
flamenco music
oh one more this might be my favorite
i mean
[Music]
what were the costume fittings like for
that i wonder short
very short after
you put all there to top it all off
we're gonna have a long break
all right another challenge for you this
is a game uh we're gonna test your
acting prowess
we call this one who am i
singer in the 80s um madonna whitney
houston
there's a girl she's cindy lauper yes uh
where's a lot of gold chains was on the
18th
oh mr t gay barakas works at the north
pole
for santa rudolph uh the no no little
people
oh the elves the the the yes but
another word for powell another word for
pal
the friendly elf buddy buddy buddy yes
uh he lives with his mom in in a creepy
motel
uh norman bates you're good at this i
did a movie with him about a train
um downtown washington uh you're you're
you're
in the navy and you you you're the
leader of the ships
uh you're you're you're captain you're
an admiral you're uh you're
yes and then and then the second word
yes i i'm your friendly neighborhood uh
spinning web guy
i uh letterman yep uh uh um
i'm like that guy but i'm um oink oink
i'm i'm a little charlotte's webb had
one of these but yeah but
it's yeah but it's but but it's with the
friendly neighborhood
version it was the spider pig let's pass
i'm a material girl living in a material
world
madonna yep oh doc uh 1.21 gigawatts uh
oh your buddy on the enterprise zach
quinto spock
yep i think we killed it some
provocative would you rather questions
for you chris
would you rather never watch a movie or
never read a book again
oh jesus
oh my god i mean i guess never watch a
movie again
i mean wow would you rather only appear
in princess diaries sequels or never act
again
i would rather only appear in princess
diaries okay let's make it happen would
you rather have a horrible singing voice
and not know it or be really bad at sex
and not know it
god i don't know bad bad singing
that question's sad for the rest of your
life you can only wear a fanny pack or
only be in costume as james kirk
fanny pack and nothing else or your
full-on james kirk outfit
fanny pack and nothing else there i mean
there's
there's too much room for something
bad's gonna go in the former
i'll just dress as jfc kirk last one
this is the dakota johnson memorial
question she posed this to me on the
previous show
would you rather have a mouth full of
bees or one bee
in your butt one being my butt just no
brainer
yeah it's a no-brainer are you kidding
me a mouth full of bees
yeah is it more about not wanting the
mouth full of bees or wanting
the bee in the butt that's a provocative
question to which you will not get an
answer uh this is
again a practical answer josh don't want
a mouth full of bees
okay i'm not threatening you they're not
gonna be there
um you're threatening me my friend this
has been a joy it's always good to catch
up with you congratulations on wonder
woman 1984.
again you're always my favorite chris
you should know this
you know start a petition or something
i'm around to be fair i say that to
every other chris too just so you know
i know you do but for a second
i believed you
you